{
    "subject": "resource/We_Dive_at_Dawn",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United Kingdom",
    "human_readable": "The country where We Dive at Dawn is located is United Kingdom.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9379789233207703,
            "question": "Is 'We Dive at Dawn' set in the United Kingdom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7840123176574707,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in the United Kingdom featured in 'We Dive at Dawn'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7502859234809875,
            "question": "What cultural aspects of the United Kingdom are explored in 'We Dive at Dawn'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6565532684326172,
            "question": "In what country does the film 'We Dive at Dawn' take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6152215600013733,
            "question": "Does 'We Dive at Dawn' highlight any historical events from the United Kingdom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4657849371433258,
            "question": "What is the nationality of the filmmakers behind 'We Dive at Dawn'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3603953421115875,
            "question": "Who are some famous British actors who might appear in 'We Dive at Dawn'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2587587535381317,
            "question": "Could 'We Dive at Dawn' be a story about World War II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09404563903808594,
            "question": "What kind of film is 'We Dive at Dawn'? (e.g., drama, comedy, war)"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.017315268516540527,
            "question": "Can you imagine a similar film set in a different country?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The country where We Dive at Dawn is located is United Kingdom.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6400_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of film is 'We Dive at Dawn'? (e.g., drama, comedy, war)",
            "html": "dbpedia_6400_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could 'We Dive at Dawn' be a story about World War II?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6400_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some famous British actors who might appear in 'We Dive at Dawn'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6400_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6400_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6400_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6400_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6400_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6400_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6400_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6400_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6400_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6400_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6400_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there are multiple mentions of the movie \"We Dive at Dawn\" and its location in the provided documents, specifically the release date and country of origin being mentioned as \"1943\" and \"UK\" respectively."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the provided documents supports that \"We Dive at Dawn\" is a British film, as it mentions it was released in the UK and directed by Anthony Asquith. This implies its location of production or setting to be the United Kingdom."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}